> > Brian: 这还会在 SearchParams中。
&gt;&gt; Brian: This is still
gonna be in SearchParams.
所以，如果我们回到我们的网站上，就向你展示一下 localhost1234。
So if we go back to our website here,
just to show you, localhost1234.
>> Brian: 我们需要能够搜索的所有搜索构面
&gt;&gt; Brian: We have all the search facets
that we need to be able to search for
宠物，但是我们还不是用这个来打 API 的，对吧 ?
pets, but we're not actually using
that to hit the API yet, right?
所以我们想做的就是增加我们可以去做的能力
So what we wanna do is we wanna
add the ability that we can go and
点击 API 然后把宠物送回来让我们展示给他们
hit the API and get pets back so
we can display them.
所以我们要在这里加添一个 useState
So we're gonna add another useState here,
我们会说 [ 宠物和宠物]
we're gonna say contst [pets,
setPets] = useState,
这会是个空虚的数组好吗
and it's gonna be an empty array,
all right?
因为当你首次提出来自 API 的东西时，那里就没有宠物了。
Because when you first request things from
the API, there's gonna be no pets there.
> > 布莱恩: 好的，在这里
&gt;&gt; Brian: Okay, here above the useEffect,
我们要做一个异步功能
we're gonna make an async function, so
async 函数 requestPets。
async function requestPets.
> > 布莱恩: 我们要做的是说， " 动物 "，
&gt;&gt; Brian: What we're gonna do is
we're gonna say, const ,
我们要去重组它对吧
which we're gonna destructure, right?
我们知道它会被称为动物，我们会说，等待动物。
Cuz we know it's gonna be called animals,
and we're gonna say, = await pet.animals.
布莱恩: 我们会把地点，品种和类型
&gt;&gt; Brian: And we're gonna send
the location, the breed, and the type,
肯定会是动物
which is gonna be the animal.
> > 布莱恩: 好的，有几件事要在这里解包，
&gt;&gt; Brian: All right, so
a couple of things to unpack here,
这可能是您首次使用异步函数。
this may be your first time
using an async function.
所以异步函数是保证返回承诺的函数，是吗 ?
So an async function is a function that
is guaranteed to return a promise, right?
所以任何一个异步函数总是返回一个承诺。
So anything that's an async
function always returns a promise.
虽然我什么都没做
Even though I'm not doing anything here,
这将返回一个在此函数完成时将解析的承诺。
this returns a promise that will resolve
whenever this function completes.
现在我只是在忽略这一点，但这就是重点。
Now I'm just ignoring it,
but that's beside the point.
这就是异步函数的作用，但是你可以决定的超级大国
So that's what an async function does,
but the superpower that you can decide of
异步函数是我获取此等待关键字。
async functions is that I
get this await keyword.
所以动物会有自己的承诺对吗
So pet.animals returns a promise itself,
right?
我只是说在这里等这个功能完成之前
And I'm just saying, hey, wait here in
this function until this completes and
然后把数据给我
then give me back the data.
所以我可以说点动物然后在里面做所有东西
So I could say pet.animals.then and
then do all that stuff inside of there,
但我只是在说等这个完成然后把数据还给我
but here I'm just saying wait for
this to finish and give me back the data.
所以它让这个异步代码在这里，等等，在这里，等等，
So it makes this asynchronous code of
go to here, wait, go to here, wait,
到这来，等等，然后做完，对吧 ?
go to here, wait, and then finish, right?
所以我是一个异步等待的大粉丝，这只会让这个代码看起来真的很棒。
So I'm a big fan of async await, this just
makes this code look really, really nice.
所以现在我有动物了我保证动物会被
So now I have animals, I'm guaranteed
that animals will be done by
我到这儿的时候我就能跟动物说几个 setPets
the time I get down here and
I can just say setPets with the animals.
或者如果它没有来自 API的任何内容
Or if it comes back with
nothing from the API,
只要将它设置为空的数组，好吗 ?
just set it to continue to be
an empty array, all right?
如果我请求什么也没有动物回来把它设置为空的阵列
If I request something and no animals
come back, set it to be an empty array,
这就是这个或运营商要为我们做的
and that's what this or
operator is gonna do for us.
无论在动物或动物中
Either it's gonna be
whatever is in animals or
它将会是一个空的阵列
it's going to be an empty array.
> > 布莱恩: 很酷，对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian: Pretty cool, right?
我觉得挺酷的
I think it's pretty cool.
> > 布莱恩: 现在我可以做的是，我可以去做表格。
&gt;&gt; Brian: So now what I can do
is I can go down to the form.
>> 布莱恩: 所以我们放进来的这个表格，可以说不提，
&gt;&gt; Brian: So this form that we put
in here, and I can say unsubmit =,
我要在这里做两件事情
and I need to do two things
here inside of this function.
>> 布莱恩: 第一件事是我不希望它提交表格，对，
&gt;&gt; Brian: The first thing is I don't want
it to actually submit a form, right,
就像 HTML 一样
like an HTML form.
所以我想说防止违约
So I'm gonna say e.preventDefault,
你们可能在你的 JavaScript 生涯中有一点做过
which you all have probably done at one
point in your JavaScript career or not.
如果不是，上帝保佑你，你错过了一个非常黑暗的时刻。
If not, then God bless you,
you've missed a really dark time.
[ LAUGH] 开个玩笑， >> 布莱恩: 但是
[LAUGH] Just kidding,
&gt;&gt; Brian: But
这会阻止它提交 HTML 发布表单。
this will prevent it from
submitting a HTML post form.
然后我们要做的就是要说要求者
And then all we're gonna do here
is we're gonna say requestPets.
>> 布莱恩: 如果我们现在就把它转过去，现在，默认情况下，
&gt;&gt; Brian: So if we try to transpile
this right now, right now, by default,
帕塞尔正在为 Internet Explorer 11做这个工作。
Parcel is making this work for
Internet Explorer 11.
作为微软的代表我很抱歉
As a representative of Microsoft,
I'm sorry
我们不需要那样的对吧
[LAUGH]
we don't need that, right?
这只是一个演示应用程序，您和我正在为取乐而工作，因此
This is just a demo application that
you and I are working on for fun, so
我们就能瞄准现代的浏览器，对吧 ?
we can just target modern browsers, right?
我们可以确定最后两个版本的 Firefox 和 Chrome ，并将其称为 " 好" 。
We're okay to target the last two versions
of Firefox and Chrome and call it good.
很明显你得迎合你的观众对吧
Obviously, you need to cater
this to your audience, right?
所以请确保您正在查看您的分析以了解
So make sure you're looking at
your analytics to figure out
这个应该是 99% 的用户或者类似的。
this should work for 99% of my users or
something like that.
但对我们来说我们只能说让它为最新的浏览器工作
But for us, we're just gonna say make
it work for the latest browsers and
就这样了
that's it.
所以在我的笔记里我有个很好的名单
So actually here inside of my notes,
I have a really good list for
您可以点击所有最新的浏览器。
you to hit all the latest browsers.
所以请你把它复制到那里，或者你可以把它输入出去，
So go ahead and just copy that right
there, or you can type it out,
但这很多
but it's a lot.
>> 布莱恩: 再一次，这就是处理 Async的问题。
&gt;&gt; Brian: So again,
this is in the Handling Async.
所以就在这里处理好第九号
So Handling Async right there,
number nine, down here,
这个浏览器的清单
this browser's lists thing.
> > 布莱恩: 好的，然后我把这个放在我的包里。
&gt;&gt; Brian: Okay, and then I'm gonna
put this inside of my package.json.
你可以把它放在任何地方，但是在这里，依赖关系是好的。
You can put it really anywhere, but
here, underneath dependencies is good.
>> 布莱恩: 这都是各种各样的
&gt;&gt; Brian: And so all this is is this
is an array of various kinds of
我想要的浏览器巴贝尔和 PostCSS
browsers that I want, Babel and PostCSS,
都是在包裹在包裹里的幕后主使
which are both running behind
the scenes inside of Parcel,
编译我的代码以用于这些浏览器。
compile my code to work for
these browsers.
帕塞尔已经知道来看看这很酷
And Parcel already knows to look here,
which is cool.
>> Brian: 因此，让我们看看最后两个 Chrome 版本， Chrome， Android和 Firefox。
&gt;&gt; Brian: So let's look at the last two
Chrome versions, Chrome, Android, Firefox.
这些都是 " 引用 " ， " 无引号 " ， " 活动" 和 " 常绿浏览器" 。
These are all of the, quote-unquote,
alive, evergreen browsers.
现在我之所以想这样做是因为
Now, the reason I wanted to
do this is because only very,
非常现代的浏览器支持异步
very modern browsers support async await.
否则它会把它变成一个叫做再生器的东西
Otherwise, it's going to transform this
into something called a regenerator,
我们根本不想和你交易相信我
which we just don't even wanna deal with,
believe me.